So he can call them whatever he wants,
because that's the freedom of speech.
He can even discourage.
He's threatened to imprison reporters.
He wants to imprison.
He said reporters should go to prison for reporting.
He threatened some of them with prison rape.
That is against the First Amendment.
OK.
How is that against the First Amendment?
You don't think sending reporters to prison
for reporting that he doesn't like?
Did he do that?
He wanted to.
He said so.
I would like them to go.
I would really like to fight.
So other people stopped him.
Doesn't mean he's not defying the Constitution.
He also said if you turn up.
Excuse me.
He can want to do something.
Yes.
Just doesn't mean he will or he can.
OK.
And I think he's very aware of that.
Well, I've already given an example of something
he did do to the Associated Press, but OK.
Yeah, OK.
So the Associated Press isn't allowed
in the Oval Office, which is his office.
That's his executive space.
And they are allowed in the press room, just like CNN,
just like The Guardian.
Which he thinks are illegal media organizations.